

CONTACT



+38971244797



k.arapov1994@gmail.com



arapovk.com



Krushevska Republika 114 2400 Strumica North Macedonia

SKILLS

- Media Buying
- CRO
- Leadership
- Project Management
- Market Research
- Web Design / Photoshop

LANGUAGE

- English
- Macedonian (Native)
- Bulgarian
- Serbian
- Croatian
- Bosnian
- German (Beginner)

KRISTIJAN ARAPOV

FACEBOOK ADS EXPERT | DIGITAL MARKETING
CONSULTANT & STRATEGIST

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Over 5 years of experience in marketing & more than \$10m+ in spend on Facebook Ads, I have helped with supporting, leading, and implementing marketing strategies to capture new markets which will increase profitability.

Creating, optimizing & scaling Facebook ads campaigns is my area of expertise. I also have a substantial amount of expertise in managing paid search and paid social campaigns including but not limited to: Google Ads, TikTok Ads, Twitter Ads, and LinkedIn Ads.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Media Buyer - Freelance February 2017 - Present

Built and managed multiple marketing campaigns for clients across different niches. Worked with affiliate marketing, dropshipping, eCommerce, SaaS & variety of black hat / gray hat offers.

Successfully managed clients ad spend of \$10m+ on Facebook alone & \$2m+ on multiple platforms. Gained a lot of experience in CRO, e-mail marketing, influencer marketing & different strategies for scaling marketing campaigns from the ground.

Head of Marketing - Regimen | Full Time Jul 2021 - April 2022

Overseeing marketing performance & analytics on different platforms such as Facebook, Google, Instagram, Apple Search ads, Outbrain & TrafficJunky. Monitor and manage digital campaigns, and provide recommendations based on performance. The startup didn't have any marketing presence and the marketing presence was crucial for providing inputs for different consumer insights, advertising methods, and their results in an effort to continually improve results & grow.

Media Buyer - SM Commerce | Contract April 2021 - Jul 2021

Managing multiple client's ad accounts from \$10,000/month to - \$100,000/month in different niches such as Beauty, Pets, Home Decor, SaaS, Motorbikes, etc. Assist with the preparation, development, execution, and monitoring of media plans.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Media Buyer - Nazim Consulting | Contract October 2020 - April 2021

Built and managed a portfolio of media campaigns for over 5 client accounts. Actively optimized and exceeded ROI targets through effective development and execution of media strategies. Mentored and managed a creative team of 3 employees to drive a creative testing roadmap along with developing engaging content and creative assets.

Media Buyer - Sugatan | Contract May 2020 - February 2021

Participate in the creative development process for channels managed by the team. Assist with the preparation, development, execution, and monitoring of media plans. Also, communicated test results and recommendations from programs with the senior management team. Increased revenue through efficient implementation of best practices for bidding, budget management, ad operations, and reporting.

Administrative Assistant - Hyconic | Full Time June 2018 - January 2019

Helping the admin team with the preparation of multiple excels & spreadsheets for marketing performance for the junior team.

Secretary - Vizba Valandovo | Part Time July 2017 - December 2017

Waiter - Sub Club | Full Time October 2016 - June 2017

Cyber Cafe Assistant - Relic Gaming Center | Full Time June 2014 - August 2014

Waiter - Pizza Restaurant Dion | Full Time May 2013 - September 2013

EDUCATION

University of Goce Delchev - Mechanical Engineering

September 2013 - September 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

Facebook & Instagram Marketing Course - Roccad Agency

May 2019

BPM Method - Depesh Mandalia

April 2021

Dropshipping Masterclass - Udemy

May 2018

AutoCAD 2D & 3D - Udemy

March 2017